petstyle.com 2014-05-22

# Privacy Policy | PetStyle

**Privacy Policy**

Information Collection and Use  
PetStyle.com understands and respects your concerns about privacy. At the same time, we do ask that you provide us information about yourself or your business so that we can help tailor your experience at PetStyle.com to your interests.  We created this Privacy Policy to provide you with information on what we may collect, and how such information may be used or shared with third parties.  Pet Entertainment Network, Inc.  is the sole owner of the information collected at [www.PetStyle.com](http://www.petstyle.com/ "www.PetStyle.com"). We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways that differ from those disclosed in this Policy. 

Personal Information You May Provide To Us:  Member Registration  
In order to use some of the services of this website, a User must first complete the registration form located at: my.petstyle.com, and become a “Member.”

During registration you are asked to provide contact information, a User name, password and additional information about yourself or your company and, possibly about your pet(s).  Registration at our site is completely voluntary and therefore you are never required to give us information about you unless you want to register and become a Member.  We hope you will register because participating in our various forums, interactive programs and other promotions or programming will help to enhance your experience at PetStyle.com. 

Personal Information We Collect Automatically:  Cookies, Log Files, IP Addresses, Etc.  
Some of our pages require the use of “cookies” for navigation, or for filling out forms.  Cookies allow us to track the movements of both Members and non-Members in order to target the interests of our Users and enhance the experience on our site.  Also, cookies enable us to maintain security by ensuring we only allow registered Members into certain areas of our site.  Once you register with our website, your usage of some “Members only” content is monitored or tracked by use of a cookie.  Cookies are or may also be used to collect information about you or your use of the site such as:  your Internet protocol (IP) address; connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, clickstream to, through, and from our web site, and products you viewed or searched for.  In addition, if you register and are a Member, a cookie will be used to collect your login information, e‑mail address; and password.  You can remove cookies from your computer by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. (However, if you do so, you may need to re-enter your information or log in with us each time you return).  If you or your browser reject(s) cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited.

  Why Do We Collect Information About You?  
We may use your information for the purposes for which you specifically provided it, including, for example, to enable us to process, validate and verify registrations of Members and access to “Members only content.”  With your permission, we may also use the information we collect through the registration process to send you newsletters or e-mail notifications about our new or existing products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you, to enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services.  (See below, “Newsletters and Other Communications With You”).

We also use the information we collect to provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our User base and usage patterns, and/or to allow us and our advertisers to personalize or target the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences.  In particular, we use information to allow advertising banners on our website to be targeted, in aggregate, to the Users for whom they are most pertinent. This means that Users see advertising that is most likely to interest them, and advertisers display their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer's experience and the effectiveness of the ads. In this statistical analysis and banner advertisement targeting, we will disclose information to third parties only in aggregate form.  Advertisers will never receive personally identifiable information about any User or Member unless a User or Member expressly consents to such disclosure.

We may also use your personal information for internal analysis purposes, including analysis to improve customer relationships.  Again, however, personal information about you as an individual will not be provided to any third party without your consent, except under the circumstances described in this Privacy Policy.  If you would like more information about our practice of collecting information for purposes of targeted advertising, or to opt out of having this information used by third-party ad servers to provide targeted ads, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp> .

Sharing our Information and Statistics  
Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, no personally identifiable information about you will be shared without your express consent.  We may use a third party provider to help collect and analyze User activities and experiences on our website.  Any sharing with a third party provider would be for our internal use only, and such third parties would either:  a) not receive personally identifiable information about users; and/or b) be subject to confidentiality provisions precluding disclosure of information.  We also may share our website’s traffic information with our partners and advertisers but do not share personal information that can identify any of our Members or Users.

Surveys or Contests  
From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site.  Those activities may be managed by a third party provider of such services, and where such activities are managed by a third party, the contest rules or survey invitation will disclose that information to users.  If you participate in contests or surveys, your participation may depend upon obtaining certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. 

Except as may be agreed to or disclosed in relevant rules or invitations to participate, we will only use the information you provide to notify contest winners, to monitor site traffic or to analyze survey results.  We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.  However, users should be aware that third party contest or survey managers (as mentioned above) may have a separate policy or posted rules about how user information may be used.  Users are therefore strongly encouraged to read all disclosures carefully and completely before participating in any third party contest or survey.

  Newsletters and Other Communications With You  
Members who are interested may elect to receive communications from PetStyle.  These communications may include newsletters, video, or other data feeds and email communication about our services and promotions.  In order to engage in these communications, we will collect, maintain and use your name and email address.  Out of respect for your privacy, we will always provide you a way to unsubscribe to these communications.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” message in any email we send you, or change your Member preferences at any time.  
Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies and log files, to create a “profile” of your preferences in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you.  We may share your profile in aggregate form only with advertisers and partners.  Again, no personally identifiable data about you is shared without your prior consent, except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy.

Circumstances Under Which We May Share Your Personally Identifiable Data (Please Read)

Legal Compliance  
We may disclose personal information about you if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to:  (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our Users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).

Sale or Closing of PetStyle.com  
We may disclose personal information about you in the event we sell our company and all or most of its assets to another service provider (or, in the unlikely event that PetStyle goes out of business or enters bankruptcy).  However, in the event that we sell our business or otherwise transfer our assets in the event of any bankruptcy, either PetStyle or the acquirer will undertake reasonable efforts to provide Users and Members an opportunity to “opt out” of registrations to the buyer’s/acquiror’s site and/or to remove themselves from association with the services or the activities of the new site.

Links and Video Services  
This web site contains links to other sites such as pet professionals, pet product manufactures, authors, and breeders, etc.  Please be aware that The Pet Entertainment Network, Inc. is not responsible for the information, privacy statements or content of any external sites.

Use of Forums  
If you use a bulletin board, “posting page,” or a forum on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there may be visible, read, collected, or used by other Users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.  In particular, please note that while using such forums, your username, nickname, and password may be displayed to other Users.  We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit or display in these forums or services.

Our Members  
The PetStyle.com site is intended for Users who are 13 years of age or older.  If you are under the age of 13, we ask that you use this site and provide registration information only with the supervision of a parent or guardian.

Security  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to protect the information we collect online.  In addition, Members’ information is password protected.  Members are solely responsible for protecting against disclosure of passwords to friends, family or others who may be exposed to Member’s information or computer.  If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to:  [customerservice@petstyle.com](mailto:customerservice@petstyle.com).

Editing Personal  / Company Information  
Updates or changes to a Member’s account and contact information can be accomplished at any time either by signing in at: [http://my.PetStyle.com](http://my.petstyle.com/ "http://my.PetStyle.com") and making those changes, or by contacting PetStyle.com at PetStyle, Attention Member Services, 2875 N.E. 191st Street, Suite 400, Aventura, Florida 33180.  Should a Member forget signin in information, it can be requested by emailing us at customerservice@petstyle.com.  Should you wish to cancel your registration at any time simply contact us at [customerservice@petstyle.com](mailto:customerservice@petstyle.com) or by writing PetStyle, Attention Member Cancellation, 2875 N.E. 191st Street, Suite 400, Aventura, Florida 33180.

Contacting Us  
Should you have any questions about this policy, our site, or your data, please contact:  customerservice@petstyle.comor write to us at PetStyle, Attention Privacy Policy, 2875 N.E. 191st Street, Suite 400, Aventura, Florida 33180.  You may also call as at 305.370.7112.

Privacy Policy Updates  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 5, 2008.  Notice of changes to this privacy policy will be provided by email if you have given same to us at registration.  Visitors and Members are strongly encouraged to check back often for changes to our privacy policy.
